<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Rift's World]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib\media\favicon.jpg</url><title>Rift's World</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 21:36:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib\rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 21:36:12 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[Timeline]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br> pre<br> 17th century Origins of coffee The modern version of roasted coffee originated in Arabia. During the 13th century, coffee was extremely popular with the Muslim community for its stimulant powers, which proved useful during long prayer sessions. By parching and boiling the coffee beans, rendering them infertile, the Arabs were able to corner the market on coffee crops. In fact, tradition says that not a single coffee plant existed outside of Arabia or Africa until the 1600s, when Baba Budan, an Indian pilgrim, left Mecca with fertile beans fastened to a strap across his abdomen. Baba’s beans resulted in a new and competitive European coffee trade. 17th century Europe and coffeeIn 1616, the Dutch founded the first European-owned coffee estate in Sri Lanka, then Ceylon, then Java in 1696. The French began growing coffee in the Caribbean, followed by the Spanish in Central America and the Portuguese in Brazil. European coffee houses sprang up in Italy and later France, where they reached a new level of popularity. Now, it is de&amp;nbsp;_rigueur_&amp;nbsp;for Parisians to indulge in a cup of coffee and a baguette or croissant at the numerous coffee cafes throughout Paris.
Copy]]></description><link>Test\Timeline.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Test/Timeline.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 21:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Welcome]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This is your new vault.<br>Make a note of something, <a data-href="create a link" href="\create a link" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">create a link</a>, or try <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://help.obsidian.md/Plugins/Importer" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="https://help.obsidian.md/Plugins/Importer" target="_blank">the Importer</a>!<br>When you're ready, delete this note and make the vault your own.<br>BOBER KURWA<br>BOBER KURWA]]></description><link>Welcome.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Welcome.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 21:33:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>